[SoloKeys Europe now online! Order your Solo 2 at SoloKeys.eu today!!!](https://solokeys.eu/)

Close Menu

Open Menu

Privacy policy
==============

**Here at SoloKeys.com we take personal privacy very seriously. As a general rule SoloKeys.com does not collect your personal information unless you chose to provide that information to us. When you choose to provide us with your personal information, you are giving SoloKeys.com your permission to use that information for the stated purposes listed in this privacy policy. If you choose not to provide us with that information, it might limit the features and services that you can use on this website.**

Changes to This Policy
----------------------

We may update this Policy from time to time. If we do, we’ll let you know about any material changes, either by notifying you on the Site or by sending you an email. New versions of this Policy will never apply retroactively — we’ll tell you the exact date they go into effect. If you keep using SoloKeys.com after a change, that means you accept this Policy.

How This Policy Applies
-----------------------

This Policy describes the information we collect from you, how we use that information and our legal basis for doing so. It also covers whether and how that information may be shared and your rights and choices regarding the information you provide to us. If you see a capitalized word, it’s defined in our Terms of Use. We use cookies and similar technologies, as described in our Cookie Policy.

By using our Website and product, you consent to policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use our Website or product. SoloKeys.com can be contacted via email at [\[email protected\]](https://solokeys.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). In order for you to access our product through SoloKeys.com and use our Services, we need to collect and process certain information.

Our Collection of Your Personal Data
------------------------------------

SoloKeys.com collects and uses information that, alone or in combination with other information, could be used to identify you (“Personal Data”) in order to inform you of various opportunities, enable sales of products through SoloKeys.com, and provide product support as described below (please also see the “How We Use Information” section below). SoloKeys.com intends to only collect and only requests that you provide to us, business and professional information about you, and not your personal contact information or other information about your personal life.

### Personal Data That You Voluntarily Provide to Us

SoloKeys.com primarily collects Personal Data provided to us by you when you interact with our offerings. For example, you may voluntarily provide us with Personal Data when you sign up to receive updates from our mailing list, call or email us directly, request an overview of our benefits, or submit your business card. The types of Personal Data that we collect vary based on the benefits offered on the Website, but generally include your name, address, telephone number, company name, job title, e-mail address, and other information that you voluntarily submit to us. You should carefully consider whether you wish to submit Personal Data. You should also review any additional terms and conditions that may govern your use of our services.

### Automatically Collected Data.

As you interact on our Website, we may collect information about your computer or device and visits to our Website (“Automatically Collected Data”) through cookies, web beacons and other technologies, Internet Protocol (IP) address tracking/URL tracking, and other tools (collectively, “Tracking Technologies”). The types of Automatically Collected Data collected on our Websites through the use of these and other tools that we may add from time to time may include: the search terms you used, new or returning user information, browser information, computer or device type, operating system, internet service provider, website usage, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, number of clicks, and ads viewed. Please see the “Tracking Technologies” section below to learn more about how we use Tracking Technologies.

Sensitive Information
---------------------

We ask that you not send or otherwise disclose to us your racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, criminal background, or trade union membership. Where you provide us with such information, we reserve the right to erase any such information at our discretion.

Children
--------

The Websites and Apps are not intended for use by or targeted at children under 18, and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 18. Children under 18 should not use the Website or Apps.

Intended Uses of Information We Collect
---------------------------------------

Provide our offerings and respond to requests. We use the Personal Data we collect from you (unless otherwise restricted by law) to: Respond directly to your information requests (including registrations or other specific requests) or other inquiries. For EU Data Subjects, such use is necessary to respond to or implement your request prior to entering into a contract with us and/or for our legitimate interest of providing good customer service and providing information about our products and services.

### Marketing.

We also use your contact information to contact you by email, postal mail, phone, or social platforms regarding information that we think may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive marketing materials, brochures, or emails from SoloKeys.com, you may inform us of your preference by sending a letter or calling SoloKeys.com at the contact information listed at the bottom of this policy. You may also submit a contact form electronically through the Website and unsubscribe from our marketing communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of our e-mails.

Where required by the applicable law, we will send you marketing information or notifications only with your consent, which was given at the time you provided us with the Personal Data. In such case, if you do not provide us with your consent to the processing of your Personal Data for this purpose, we will not send you this information. Otherwise, we will send you marketing information and notifications to further our legitimate interest of promoting our products and services and identifying ways to grow our business. For California residents, please consult the “Your Privacy Rights” section below for additional considerations.

With your permission, we may also use information you provide to us as a testimonial posted on the Websites.

### Correspondence.

If you correspond with SoloKeys.com via e-mail, the postal service, our web forms, social platforms, or other form of communication, we may retain the correspondence and the information it contains. We may use the information for business purposes, including responding to your inquiry, notifying you of SoloKeys.com related opportunities, and other marketing purposes (please read the Marketing section above for more information on our marketing practices and how to opt out or unsubscribe).

Keep in mind that email transmissions are not encrypted by default, so we suggest you do not send sensitive information such as Social Security numbers, credit card numbers, or bank account information via such contact forms.

If such information is required, it will be via a web page that clearly states the page and its transmission of information is secure and encrypted. All electronic messages received from visitors are deleted when no longer needed.

### URL and IP Address.

SoloKeys.com collects information about users’ IP addresses, including users’ utilization of our Website, to help us design our Website to better suit our Website users’ needs. We may use information about your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Website, analyze trends, track visitor movements, and gather information that assists us in identifying visitor preferences. We also may use your IP address to enhance our security and investigate an actual or potential security incident. For EU Data Subjects, this use of your information is necessary for our legitimate interests in understanding how the Website and our Services are being used by you, to improve your experience on it and ensuring network and information security. For more information about what we mean by legitimate interests, and when we may process Personal Data for our legitimate interests, please see the “EU Data Subjects” section below.

### Aggregated Data.

We may also compile, anonymize and/or aggregate Personal Data and other information collected about Websites’ visitors, as described in this Privacy Policy, and use such anonymized and/or aggregated data for our business purposes, including disclosing such data to our partners, service providers, advertisers and/or other third parties for marketing or promotional purposes. This aggregate information does not identify you. For EU Data Subjects, per the GDPR, this use of your Personal Data is necessary for our legitimate interests in understanding how the Websites and our products and services are being used by you and to improve your experience on it. For more information about what we mean by legitimate interests, and when we may process Personal Data for our legitimate interests, please see the “EU Data Subjects” section below.

### Social Media and Third Party Data

SoloKeys.com uses commenting and social media plug-ins and third-party websites. We use those third-party services to interact with visitors and to build our community on social media. We also use these third-party services to measure the number of visitors to our website, to interact with visitors on the site, and to make our website more useful to visitors.

In such cases, the third-party application may request an email address, username, password, internet protocol (IP) address, and geographic location for account registration or sign-in purposes. SoloKeys.com does not use those third-party websites or services to collect personal information from individuals. Any personal information collected by the third-party website will not be stored or transmitted by SoloKeys.com. SoloKeys.com has no control over or access to specific login information or any other sensitive personal information provide to third-party websites.

SoloKeys.com also uses third-party analytics services (like Google Analytics) to gather this information for analysis.

Data Processing
---------------

Google Analytics (Google Inc.) Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of Sticker Mule, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy – Opt Out. Managing contacts and sending messages

Managing contacts and sending messages
--------------------------------------

MailChimp (The Rocket Science Group, LLC.) MailChimp is an email address management and message sending service provided by The Rocket Science Group, LLC.

Personal Data collected: email address.

Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.

Managing Product Sale and Payments
----------------------------------

Kickstarter, PBC Kickstarter is a crowd funding service that enables users to establish accounts with the purpose of supporting or initiating kickstarter campaigns and processing payments as needed to fulfill pledges.

Personal Data collected: privacy policy

Place of processing: United States

Airbrite, Inc.

Airbrite, Inc.(Trycelery.com) develops and operates a platform for pre-orders, custom crowdfunding, and e-commerce. Its platform allows users to track, measure, and iterate their paid channels; and provides various tools for advance sales, and customer and order management.

Personal Data collected: [privacy policy](https://help.trycelery.com/tos "privacy policy")

Place of processing: United States

Generally, the information requested by SoloKeys.com will be used to support your experience using the SoloKeys.com product, or a website feature or service to you, such as commenting, support, or providing future content better tailored to your interests.

Cookie Policy
-------------

SoloKeys.com uses cookies to provide a customized user experience on the site. A cookie is a small file that a website transfers to your computer to allow your browser to remember information about your last session on that website. Your computer only shares information in the cookie with the specific website that provided it, and no other website can request that information. SoloKeys.com collects and temporarily stores certain information about your visit to help us to better align our content and the website design with your needs. The information these cookies collect includes:

1. The domain you access our website from
2. Your computer’s IP address
3. The date and time you accessed the site
4. The operating system of your computer
5. The browser you’re using to access our site
6. The Universal Resource Locators (URLs) of the pages you visit on our website
7. Your username, if you’ve logged into the site
8. The URL of site you came from, if you clicked a link there that brought you to our website

We may share this information internally with SoloKeys.com employees or third-party contractors as needed. This information is only used to improve the website and enhance our visitors’ experience. Raw data logs are only retained temporarily for site management purposes.

Security Measures
-----------------

SoloKeys.com takes the security of your personal information very seriously. We are committed to reasonable precautions to ensure that the information we collect is secure and inaccessible by anyone outside of our organization. These precautions include advanced access controls to limit access to that information to only internal personnel who require access to that information. Our security measures are regularly upgraded and tested to ensure they are effective. We take the following specific steps to protect your information:

Use internal access controls so only limited personnel have access to your information. Anyone with access to user information is trained on all relevant security and compliance policies. Servers that store visitor information are regularly backed up to protect against loss. All information is secured through modern security technologies like secure socket layer (SSL), encryption, firewalls, and secure passwords.

All access safeguards described above are in place to prevent unauthorized access by outsiders to information stored on or transmitted by our systems.

European Union Users
--------------------

Data protection law in Europe requires a “lawful basis” for collecting and retaining personal information from citizens or residents of the European Economic Area. Our lawful bases include: Performing the contract we have with you: In certain circumstances, we need your personal data to comply with our contractual obligation to deliver a product, i.e. when you buy a product online.

Legitimate interests: This is a technical term in data protection law which essentially means we have a good and fair reason to use your data and we do so in ways which do not hurt your interests and rights. We sometimes require your data to pursue our legitimate interests in a way that might reasonably be expected as part of running our business and that does not materially impact your rights, freedom or interests.

For example, we may send you promotional communications or updates about our Services and Products, subject to your right to control whether we do so.

Additionally, we analyze how users interact with our Site so we can understand better what elements of the design are working well and which are not working so well. This allows us to improve and develop the quality of the online experience we offer all our users.

Your Data Rights and Choices
----------------------------

You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

Ask for a list of personal information we have about you, if any. This can be provided within a reasonable time. Request a change, correction, or deletion of your personal information. Request that we avoid collecting anything in the future (opt-out).

Requests typically receive a response within thirty (30) days. If access cannot be provided within that time frame, we will provide the requesting party with an estimated date by which the information will be provided. If for some reason access is denied, we will provide an explanation of why access has been denied.

If you do not wish to have cookies stored on your machine, you have the option to turn cookies off in your browser. However, keep in mind that turning off cookies may impact how this website functions. Disabling browser cookies will also impact how other websites you visit store browser cookies as well.

California Privacy Rights In addition to the information provided in this Privacy Policy, under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide “personal information” (as defined in the statute) in obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us, once a calendar year, information about the personal information we shared, if any, with other businesses for marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of personal information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared such personal information for the immediately prior calendar year. To obtain this information, please contact us by sending a letter or calling us at the contact information below. You may also submit a contact form electronically through the Websites.

Contact Info
------------

If you believe at any point that we are not following this privacy policy as stated, please contact us immediately via email ([\[email protected\]](https://solokeys.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)), or via telephone ([508-506-1854](tel:508-506-1854)).

###### Information

© 2024 SoloKeys. All Rights Reserved
